Previously on the show.
Trong tập trước.
The sheep thought Wolffy took
Các bạn Cừu tưởng Sói Xám đã lấy
the green color pencil that was used for creating rainbows,
cây bút chì màu xanh vẽ cầu vồng,
so they tailed him secretly.
nên đã bí mật theo dõi.
But they discovered that it was a misunderstanding.
Hóa ra lại chỉ là hiểu lầm.
It turned out that the green color pencil was in Paddi's backpack all along.
Hóa ra cây bút màu xanh lại ở trong cặp của Cừu Lười.
So what will happen next?
Vậy chuyện gì sẽ xảy ra nữa đây?
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Crisis of Doppelgangers."
"ĐẢO BAY: THÁM HIỂM BẦU TRỜI: KHỦNG HOẢNG NHÂN BẢN"
Paddi!
Cừu Lười!
Where did Paddi go this early in the morning?
Cậu ấy đi đâu vào sáng sớm nhỉ?
The early bird gets the worms.
Trâu chậm uống nước đục.
Paddi, you are abusing Magic Train again.
Cừu Lười, cậu lại dùng tàu Ma Thuật.
Sorry, I won't do it again.
Xin lỗi, lần sau sẽ không dùng nữa.
It's our turn to clean today.
Hôm nay là chúng mình dọn đó.
Yes, I promise I will complete the task.
Tớ hứa sẽ hoàn thành nhiệm vụ.
The current time is 12 noon...
Giờ là 12 giờ trưa...
Oh no! The limited sale of rainbow pudding has started.
Ôi không! Bánh cầu vồng đang giảm giá.
Wait. Didn't you say we're doing the cleaning together?
Chờ đã. Không phải chúng ta sẽ dọn với nhau à?
I will use my doppelgangers to help you with the cleaning.
Tớ sẽ dùng bản sao để làm.
Oh no! I won't make it!
Không! Tớ không đến kịp mất!
Oh dear, it's Wolffy.
ÔI trời, là Sói Xám.
How about I buy you this car?
Ba mua xe này cho con nhé?
You just bought me one yesterday.
Ba mới mua một cái hôm qua mà.
How about this one?
Thế còn cái này?
You bought me that the day before yesterday too.
Ba cũng mua hôm kia rồi.
Let's look at other toys.
Thế đi xem cái khác đi.
What other toys has Willie not played with before?
Có món nào mà Sói Con chưa chơi nhỉ?
Oh, I can't think of anything.
Ôi, không nghĩ ra.
I should leave before Wolffy finds out I'm here.
Mình phải đi trước khi bị phát hiện.
No. I have to find a place to hide first.
Không. Phải tìm nơi trốn trước.
This is strange. Where did that little spaceship go?
Lạ thật. Phi thuyền tí hon đó đâu nhỉ?
Dad, I want this spaceship.
Ba, con muốn cái này.
Shop owner, I'll take this.
Tôi mua cái này.
Sure.
Được.
Great! Let's go home and play with the spaceship.
Hay quá! Về nhà chơi với nó thôi.
How did this happen?
Sao lại ra thế này?
I can finally work on my invention.
Cuối cùng cũng được yên tĩnh.
Spaceship, go...
Phi thuyền, đi...
If I knew this would happen, I'd have cleaned with Weslie.
Nếu biết trước thì đã ở lại dọn với Cừu Vui Vẻ rồi.
No. I must escape before Wolffy finds out.
Không. Phải trốn trước khi bị phát hiện.
Great. The gate is open.
Tuyệt. Cửa đang mở.
Wow! The spaceship is moving on its own again.
Ồ! Phi thuyền đang tự đi kìa.
This is strange. Did I get the recipe wrong?
Lạ thật. Là công thức sai sao?
I'm so close to escaping.
Sắp thoát rồi.
Spaceship, why are you going around? Let's play together.
Phi thuyền, ngươi đi đâu thế? Ở lại chơi đi.
How can I let Willie know I am here without letting Wolffy know?
Làm sao để Sói Con nhận ra mình mà không cho Sói Xám biết?
This is...
Đây là...
It worked. Willie recognized me.
Thành công rồi. Sói Con đã nhận ra mình.
Dad. Look. This spaceship can stack blocks on its own.
Ba. Nhìn này. Phi thuyền này có thể tự xếp hình đó.
Oh no! I can't let Wolffy find out.
Không! Không thể để Sói Xám biết.
Dad, look.
Ba, nhìn đi.
This is strange.
Lạ thật.
Willie, I'm really busy now. Go play on your own.
Sói Con, ba đang rất bận. Tự chơi đi con.
Phew!
Phù!
This way, Willie will surely understand.
Thế này thì chắc Sói Con sẽ hiểu.
Willie, look this way.
Sói Con, nhìn đây.
What did Willie draw?
Sói Con vẽ gì thế nhỉ?
Great! Wolffy left.
Tuyệt! Sói Xám đi rồi.
Now I can tell Willie my identity openly.
Giờ thì có thể nói cho Sói Con rồi.
Willie, look this way.
Sói Con, nhìn ra đây.
Willie.
Sói Con.
I give up.
Từ bỏ.
Willie, come with me. We're going out.
Sói Con, đi ra ngoài với mẹ.
Okay.
Vâng ạ.
-Let's go. -Okay.
-Đi nào. -Vâng ạ.
Good timing.
Thời cơ đến rồi.
What was that sound?
Tiếng gì thế nhỉ?
Wolffy almost found me again.
Sói Xám suýt thì phát hiện.
What should I do now? Right!
Giờ thì làm gì đây? Đúng rồi!
I didn't think they could help out with cleaning too.
Không ngờ chúng biết dọn dẹp.
Paddi!
Cừu Lười!
How come my doppelgangers are not here yet?
Sao các phân thân còn chưa đến?
This is strange. Where did the screw go?
Lạ thật. Mọi người đâu rồi?
Oh no! Wolffy is coming.
Á! Sói Xám đang đến.
I still need a hammer and an apple.
Mình cần một cái búa và một quả táo.
I'm safe finally.
Cuối cùng cũng an toàn.
Thank you, Paddi.
Cảm ơn, Cừu Lười.
The goat I have wanted to catch is right by me after all.
Cừu Nhỏ mình muốn bắt hóa ra lại luôn ởbên.
You are not getting away this time.
Đừng mong thoát.
They're here at last.
Chúng đây rồi.
Since you are here, let me give you a taste of my vacuum cleaner
Ngươi đã đến thì hãy nếm mùi máy hút bụi mới
that is specially designed to
được thiết kế đặc biệt để đối phó
deal with Magic Train's doppelgangers.
với các bản sao.
Wolffy, I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
Sói Xám, ngươi sẽ thất vọng thôi.
Magic Train, combine!
Tàu Ma Thuật hợp!
This was the worst combining mode I've seen.
Đây là màn hợp lại tệ nhất ta đã thấy.
What's going on?
Có chuyện gì vậy?
How come I'm one cart short?
Sao lại thiếu một cái?
You're not going anywhere.
Đừng mong ra.
Where did the last piece go?
Bản sao cuối đâu rồi?
What happened?
Cái gì vậy?
Your invention is not that good either.
Sáng chế của ngươi cũng tệ thôi.
How dare you laugh at my invention? I will show you!
Sao ngươi dám cười phát minh của ta? Xem đây!
Is Wolffy crazy?
Sói Xám điên rồi sao?
Whatever. I'll just run.
kệ đi. Phải chạy đã.
I made it.
Thành công rồi.
This is my upgraded vacuum cleaner. You're not going anywhere!
Đây là máy hút bụi cải tiến của ta. Không thoát được đâu!
Dad!
Ba!
Mom and I picked up a spaceship on the street
Con nhặt cái này trên đường
that looks exactly like the one we got at the toy store.
y hệt cái mình mua ở cửa hàng đồ chơi.
Willie is in there! Magic Train, Combine!
Cừu Vui Vẻ đây rồi! Tàu Ma Thuật, hợp!
Even if you are combined, my vacuum cleaner can suck you in.
Kể cả hợp nhất cũng sẽ bị hút thôi.
Magic Train, full power.
Tàu Ma Thuật, toàn lực.
Paddi, I'll get you!
Cừu Lười cứ chờ đấy!
Paddi, remember. Don't ever abuse Magic Train again.
Cừu Lười nhớ nhé. Đừng bao giờ lạm dụng tàu nữa.
I won't.
Sẽ không đâu.
Right, Weslie, I found something interesting.
Cừu Vui Vẻ ơi, tớ tìm thấy cái này.
Look.
Nhìn này.
Wolffy's vacuum cleaner is quite fun. It can be used for cleaning.
Máy hút bụi của Sói Xám được đó. Có thể dùng dọn dẹp.
I think it's better not to use Wolffy's things.
Tớ nghĩ tốt hơn là không dùng đồ của Sói Xám.
Ouch! Weslie, please help me.
Á! Cừu Vui Vẻ, cứu tớ.
I told you not to use it.
Tớ đã nói rồi mà.
I won't do it ever again.
Tớ sẽ không làm thế nữa đâu.
TO BE CONTINUED 2762 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
CÒN TIẾP 2762 NGÀY TỪ KHI KHỞI HÀNH